Guide to the Voices Breaking Boundaries Records
University of Houston Libraries
Voices Breaking Boundaries Records
1999-2016
2014-015
Voices Breaking Boundaries (Organization)
18.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
This collection contains materials from Voices Breaking Boundaries’ (VBB) history and administration, planning documents, event materials, press clippings and audio-visual materials.
Historical Note:
Voices Breaking Boundaries is a grassroots non-profit arts organization founded in 2000 by writer and artist Sehba Sarwar along with four other women – Marcela Descalzi, Jacsun Shah, Donna Perkins and Christine Choi. Initially the collective hosted readings at a Houston bookstore, but evolved into a dynamic, multi-disciplinary organization. Voices Breaking Boundaries art productions aim to examine issues connected to education, race, women’s right, demography and more from a global perspective.
Major productions include; La Voz Feminina, held each International Women’s Day, the Living Room art series, Words for Peace, East End Live Art and more. Voices Breaking Boundaries participated in the Houston Art Car Parade in 2010, and since 2013 have been producing publications of VBB artists and writers work.
http://www.vbbarts.org/
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Voices Breaking Boundaries (Organization)
Genre/Form of Material:
Audiovisual materials; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Financial records; Grant proposals; Photographs
Topical Term:
Art -- Exhibitions; Art -- Texas -- Houston; Artists -- Texas -- Houston; Nonprofit organizations -- Texas -- Houston
Accruals:
Additional materials acquired on September 24, 2015. Digital files were transffered on multiple occassions 2014-2016.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials from Voices Breaking Boundaries’ (VBB) history and administration, planning documents, event materials, press clippings and audio-visual materials.
In addition to paper records, this collection also contains digital archival material. Digital archival materials can be accessed in the Special Collections Reading Room by advance request. Because not all of these materials are processed, these materials may require up to two weeks to access. Some files may be restricted and not available for access at all. Contact the curator for more information.
Detailed List of Contents
- Programming for Teens
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains writing samples, paperwork, and lesson plans from camps and workshops provided to teenagers by Voices Breaking Boundaries.
  - Stories that Must be Told, 2001-2013
    - Sharpstown High School, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Furr High School - planning and budgets, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Furr High School - agenda and rosters, spring 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Furr High School - student reflections, spring 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Furr High School - student Work and course materials, spring 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Furr High School, summer 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Furr High School - course outline and agendas, fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Furr High School - student rosters, fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Furr High School - student work, fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Furr High School - student reflections, fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Furr High School - student work, fall 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Coming Together, 2004
    - Planning and materials (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Student writing and reflections (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Retelling Stories, 2005
    - Planning and administration (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Instructor reflections (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Student forms, work and reflections (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Showcase for Poetry/Prose, Art and Music (SPAM), 2006-2008
    - Student contracts and attendance, fall 2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Instructor agendas and reflections, spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Student reflections, spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Student class schedules, spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Sample poetry, spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Student writing, spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Course materials, spring 2007 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Attendance rosters, summer 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Student work and reflections, summer 2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Student reflections, summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Instructor reflections, summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Student contact information, summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Student sign-up slips, summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Consent and release forms, summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Administratrive paperwork, fall 2007-spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Blank student registration forms, fall 2007-spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Students' writing, fall 2007-spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Student reflections, fall 2007-spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Course materials, fall 2007-spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Course materials, summer and fall 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Size Sensual Sundays course materials, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Other Workshops
    - Lee High School performance project, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brave New Voices, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Writing for Self-Discovery, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Westbury High School Where is Home, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Programming for Adults and Teachers
  This series contains planning documents, lesson plans, rosters, student writing and reflections from workshops provided to adults and teachers.
  - Early Workshops, 2003-2004
    - Hualhuises, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Voices of the Displaced administration, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Voices of the Displaced course materials, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Voices of the Displaced student work and evaluations, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Teacher Writing and Trauma Training, 2006-2008
    - Planning rosters and agendas, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Course materials, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Surveys and reflections, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Planning, registration, and agendas, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Surveys and reflections, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Other Workshops, 2009-2014
    - Writing for Self-Discovery materials, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Writing for Self-Discovery planning and materials, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Writing for Self-Discovery surveys and reflections, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Writing for Self-Discovery surveys and reflections, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Borderlines materials, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Workshop Documents
    - Writing examples - prose, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Writing examples - poetry, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Teaching aides, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Administration and planning, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Student work, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Surveys and reflections, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Event Planning and Promotion
  This series contains materials related to the organization and promotion of Voices Breaking Boundaries events, art installations, and performances.
  - VBB Events
    - Poetry reading, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Travelling Film South Asia, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Words for Peace, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Between the Lines, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Crossing Borders, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Valiente: Honoring Rubén Martinez, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Words for Peace 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - A World without Water, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Dissenting Voices in Pakistan, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Houston Artists and Dissent, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Words for Peace 3: Incite Change!, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Other events, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Women with Strong Blood, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Incite Summer, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Words for Peace 4 “Voices of a People’s History", 2006 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Valiente Award: Farnoosh Moshiri, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Incite Fall Fundraiser and Silent Auction, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Andrea White Luncheon, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Houston Palestine Film Festival, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Un/Natural Disaster: Katrina-Kashmir, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - The Shootout, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Valiente Honoring Mel Chin, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Empowering Jena: Keep the Movement Moving, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - La Voz Femina 5: Lisa Hernandez, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Words for Peace 5: Condemn Invasion, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Living Room Art, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Houston Palestine Film Festival, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - East End Live Art: La Voz Femina 6, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Pakistan Live Broadcast, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Honoring Dissent/Descent, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - East End Live Art: Decade of Dissent, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Other events, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - East End Live Art: Teachers Speak Out 2, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - East End Live Art: Revisiting Un/Natural Disasters, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Valiente Award: Bapsi Sidhwa, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Art Car Sprawl: VBB Car #135 Revolution, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Third Worlds/Third Ward, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Politiqueer, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Use and Abuses of History, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Valiente: Voices of Struggle, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Teachers and Students Speak Out 4, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Women Under Siege, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Film, Food and VBB on the WWW, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Homes and Histories, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Other events, 2010-2012 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Struggles for Freedom: Arab Spring/Occupy Houston, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Jai Bhim Comrade Screening, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Teachers and Students Speak Out 5, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - La Valiente: VBB Turns 13!, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Homes and Histories Part 2, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Borderlines, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Teachers and Students Speak Out 6, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - La Valiente 2014: Writers Who Persevere (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Crossing the Lines, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Experiments with Truth, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Sebha Sarwar Presents: What is Home, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Borderlines Book Launch, 2016 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Other promotional materials, 2013-2016 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Open Mic sign-up forms, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified events, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Collaborative Events
    - Citywide Celebration of Contemporary African Art, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - School Literacy and Culture Project, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Visual Griot of Mali, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Interfaith/Pink Iftar, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - La Luz, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Women in Philanthropy, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Think Tank, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Go Neighborhoods, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - UH Presentation, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Bridging Cultures, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Other collaborative events, 2002-2015 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Event and Workshop Photographs
  This series contains unlabeled photographs and negatives from VBB workshops and events.
  - Photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Publications
  This series contains publications and literary compilations created by VBB workshop and event participants.
  - Workshop Publications
    - Making Noise, 2001 (Box 5, Item 1)
    - Stories That Must Be Told, 2002 (Box 5, Item 2)
    - Making Noise [The Anthology], 2002 (Box 5, Item 3)
    - Making Noise, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Item 4)
    - Coming Together, 2004 (Box 5, Item 5)
    - Showcase for Poetry/Prose, Art and Music (SPAM), 2007 (Box 5, Item 6)
    - The Ninth Draft: Inprint Fiction Workshop, 2011 (Box 5, Item 7)
    - Writing For Self-Discovery, 2012 (Box 5, Item 8)
    - Creative Writing Anthology Wharton K-8, 2013 (Box 5, Item 9)
    - Creative Writing Anthology Wharton K-8, 2014 (Box 5, Item 10)
    - Heartbeats: The Izzat Project, undated (Box 5, Item 11)
    - Papyrus Lee High School, undated (Box 5, Item 12)
  - Event Publications
    - Made in Palestine, 2003 (Box 5, Item 13)
    - Digital Meets Pakistani Truck Art, 2010 (Box 5, Item 14)
    - Homes and Histories, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Item 15)
    - Women Under Siege, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Item 16)
    - Borderlines Volume One, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Item 17)
    - Borderlines Volume Two, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Item 18)
- Press and Publcity
  This series contains press releases and clippings, publicity planning and general or season specific promotional materials.
  - Press releases, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, 2004-2013 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Press clippings, 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Press clippings, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Press clippings, 2008-2011 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Press clippings, 2011-2015 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Publicity Services Gish Creative, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - General promotional materials, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Season promotional materials, 2000-2016 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Partner and collaborative press, 2012, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Event Materials and Exhibits
  This series contains event materials including art pieces from various VBB events and art exhibitions.
  - Art Car Sprawl, 2010
    - Art Car headlights (Box 7, Item 1)
    - Unidentified Art Car pieces (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Art Car panel (Box 7, Item 3)
  - Women Under Siege, 2012
    - Loose Letters (Box 8, Item 1)
    - Wrapped Letters (Box 8, Item 2-5)
  - Exploring Rituals, 2013
    - Fabric Flowers - red (Box 8, Item 6)
    - Fabric Flowers - pink (Box 8, Item 7)
    - Fabric Flowers - purple (Box 8, Item 8)
    - Fabric Flowers - teal (Box 8, Item 9)
    - Fabric Flowers - green (Box 8, Item 10)
    - Fabric Flowers - yellow (Box 8, Item 11)
    - Fabric Flowers - gold and orange (Box 8, Item 12)
    - Fabric Flowers - pink and salmon (Box 8, Item 13)
  - Crossing the Lines, 2014
    - Lace fabric with beads (Box 9, Item 1)
    - 20 painted shoes from exhibition (Box 9, Item 2)
  - Other Promotional Materials
    - Archival bag with various badges and magnets, undated (Box 9, Item 3)
  - Event Posters
    - Traveling Films South Asia, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Honoring Dissent/Descent, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - A Decade of Dissent, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Patti Smith Reading “Just Kids”, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Art Car Sprawl, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - East End Live Art Shows, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Honoring Women’s Voices, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Third Worlds Third Ward, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Politiqueer, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - What’s Color Got to Do With It?, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Teachers and Students Speak Out 4, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Women Under Siege, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Exploring Rituals, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - David Barsamian Speech, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Remembering Jose Campos Torres, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Borderlines Volume 1, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Monitor 10, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - [Un]Welcome, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Oversize Event Materials
    - Photographs by Paul Hester for Homes and Histories (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Borderlines exhibits (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Other oversize event materials (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Administration
  This series contains administrative paperwork including non-profit board development, board meeting minutes, strategic development and administrative correspondence and contact information.
  - Board Development and Training
    - Board development materials, 1990-1993, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Board training materials, 1992-1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Board training materials, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Board training materials, 2003-2008 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Critical Components of Effective Governance, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HAA Management Assistance and Org Management, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Introduction to Advanced Professional Development, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Board Information, Meetings, and Strategic Planning
    - Bylaws, mission statement and agreements, 2002-2004, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Planning and development, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - FY 2001-2002 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - FY 2002-2003 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Strategic planning, 2003-2007 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - FY 2003-2004 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 2004 Board Retreat (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - FY 2004-2005 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - FY 2005-2006 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Strategic planning, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - FY 2006-2007 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 2007 Board Retreat (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - FY 2007-2008 board meetings (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - 2008 Board Retreat (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - FY 2008-2009 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Strategic planning, 2009-2011 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 2009 Board Retreat (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - FY 2009-2010 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - FY 2010-2011 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 2011 Business Plan (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 2011 Board Retreat (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - FY 2011-2012 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - FY 2012-2013 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - 2013 Board Retreat (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - FY 2013-2014 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 2014 Board Retreat (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - FY 2014-2015 board meetings (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 2015 Board Retreat (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Board materials, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Sehba's notebooks, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Contacts
    - Administrative correspondence, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Business cards and contacts, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Mailing list sign-up forms, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Human Resources
  This series contains documents related to human resources and employment such as employee manuals, job descriptions, hiring processes and correspondence, and staff and artist employment and payment records.
  - General Human Resources (HR) Documents
    - Employee manuals, 2007-2009 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Job descriptions, 2007, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Hiring and interviews, 2007-2009, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Blank HR forms, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Staff and Frequent Contributors
    - Elia Arce, 2005, 2007-2009 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Courtney Benevides, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Lisa Christianson, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Marcela Descalzi, 2003-2012 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Eric Hester, 2001-2012 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Michael Hoerman, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Shelby Hohl, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Victoria Jones, 2006-2009 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Angela Martinez, 2008-2012 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Office Assistance Management (Tanya Akpabio), 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Jasmine Rosario, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Sehba Sarwar, 2002-2012 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Emily Sketch, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Oscar Sonnen, 2004-2008 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Michael Kahlil Taylor, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Joshua Turner, 2009-2012 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Glenda White, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Artist Payments and Honorariums, 2000-2012
    - A-F (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - G-M (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - N-Z (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Contract and Temporary Employees
    - Clerical and professional, 2005-2012 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Event support and organization, 2002-2012 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Internships, 2002-2009 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Web design and marketing (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Workshop instructors, 2002-2010 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Checks - mutiple recipients, 2003-2007 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Finance and Funding
  This series contains documents related to the finances and funding of VBB, including grant applications, financial statements and tax information organized by fiscal year.
  - Grant Applications
    - Andy Warhol Foundation, 2007-2010 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Bridgeways, 2004-2007 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Brown Foundation, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Brown Foundation, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Brown Foundation, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - CACHH, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - CACHH, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - CACHH, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - CACHH, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - CACHH, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - CACHH, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - CACHH, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Cockrell Foundation, 2012-2013 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Cullen Foundation, 2012-2013 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Duncan Foundation, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Education Foundation of Harris County, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Ellwood Foundation, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Exxon Mobil, 2007-2009 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Farb Community Service Fund, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - William Stamp Farris Foundation, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Ford Foundation, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Hamman Foundation, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Hearst Foundation, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Heartland, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Herzstein Foundation, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - HAA City Initiative, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - HAA General Operating Support, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - HAA MODE ISP, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 23-24)
    - HAA City Initiative, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HAA General Operating Support Expansion, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
    - HAA MODE, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - HAA MODE Incubator, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HAA General Operating Support Expansion, 2010-2011 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HAA MODE, 2010-2011 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HAA Touring and Neighborhood Arts, 2010-2011 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HAA General Operating Support Expansion, 2011-2012 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - HAA MODE, 2011-2012 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Houston Endowment, 1999-2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Houston Endowment, 2006-2015 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Humanities Texas, 2011-2013 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Isenberg Family Charitable Trust, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - John P. McGovern Foundation, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mayor’s Office of Cultural Affairs, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - MetLife Foundation, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Mid-America Arts Alliance, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 2010-2011 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 2011-2012 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 2010-2011 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - National Fellowship Program, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Oppenheimer Foundation, 2002, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Poets and Writers, 2006-2008, 2011, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Powell Foundation, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Philanthropy, 2008-2009 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Rockwell Funds, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Samuels Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Simmons Foundation, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Simmons Foundation, 2011-2013 (Box 20, Folder 10)